William Safire Papers
William Safire Papers
- Media
  - Video cassettes
    - Other television programs, may or may not feature Safire; titles used are those written on the item
      - West Wing, 1999 September 22 (Oversize 24)
      - Barbara Walters "Biography", 2000 October 15 (Oversize 24)
      - NY Times DC Bureau, The Best Times NARC, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 24)
      - NY Times DC Bureau, The Best Times Pilot, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 24)
      - NY Times DC Bureau, The Best Times Volley Ball, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 24)
      - NY Times DC Bureau, Two Marriages Connections, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 25)
      - NY Times DC Bureau Two Marriages Legacy/ Commitments/ Reflections, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 25)
      - NY Times DC Bureau Two Marriages Reunion, 2001 March 29 (Oversize 25)
      - Pancetta Lecture Series, 2002 April 1 (Oversize 25)
      - A & E Biography, Barbara Walters, A Driving Force, undated; 2 videos (Oversize 25)
      - A & E Biography, Nixon, undated; 2 videos (Oversize 25)
      - "The Alistair Cooke Salute with unedited personal greetings", undated (Oversize 25)
      - As it Happened: From Chappaquiddick to the Moon: A Fateful Weekend, undated (Oversize 25)
      - "Maralee Beck news tape", 2 copies (Oversize 25)
      - "Roy Cohn: Joe McCarthy's Right Hand Man" on A & E Biography, undated (Oversize 25)
      - "The Stab", undated (Oversize 25)
      - "WNYC-TV, New York presents The Kwitny Report, Poland" parts 1 and 2, undated (Oversize 25)
    - Taped events
      - Awards Banquet of William Safire on C-SPAN, 1986 April 11 (Oversize 25)
      - "The Wannsee Conference for Dickson, Shapiro, and Morin", 1989 February 17 (Oversize 26)
      - RESN Republican Neighborhood Meeting, highlights, 1993 May 3 (Oversize 26)
      - Cazenovia College Commencement, 1994 (Oversize 26)
      - "Pacific University Debate" on C-SPAN, 1995 February 22 (Oversize 26)
      - The William Safire Roast for Spina Bifida, 1998 October 1; 3 videos (Oversize 26)
    - Miscellaneous
      - "Gayle Jessup II", 1983 (Oversize 26)
      - Quayle's Air, 1991 October 18 (Oversize 26)
      - "Helene Safire", 1992 (Oversize 26)
      - "On Language Program with shorts with scratch track", 2003 October 15 (Oversize 26)
      - Admiral Inman, undated (Oversize 26)
      - "The Man from U.N.C.L.E.", undated (Oversize 26)